DEDEN KURNIA

Panunggangan Utara,
Tangerang
dedenkurnia001@gmail.com
089663758497

Programmer

Summary

I am a graduate with a Bachelor's degree in Information Systems, with work experience in IT support and programming. I am proficient in operating both software and hardware, application development, and network installation. I possess strong integrity, adaptability to diverse work environments, a strong work ethic, and initiative.

Skill Highlights

- Microsoft Office
- PHP Developer
- Wordpress Developer
- Network Installation
- Software & Hardware Installation
- Flutter UI
- SQL
- db2
- SQL server
- MySQL

- HTML
- CSS
- CI

Experience

IT Staff - 07/2019 to 01/2021

PT. Putra Mustika Prima (MPM Parts)

- Maintenance hardware.
- Troubleshoot hardware software user.
- Monitoring network.
- Asset management IT.
- Inventory management (Microsoft AX Dynamic)

IT Support - 01/2021 to 02/2021

Pasifik group internasional

- Web developer (company profile).
- Graphic design.

IT Admin - 03/2021 to 12/2022

PT. Karya citra cemerlang (KCC)

- Entri data.
- Monitoring stock.
- Troubleshoot hardware software user.

IT Support - 01/2023 to 05/2024

PT INDO TAICHEN TEXTILE INDUSTRY

- Monitoring stock.
- Troubleshoot hardware & software user.
- Installed LAN network.
- Installed CCTV network.

Programmer- 05/2024 to Now PT INDO TAICHEN TEXTILE INDUSTRY

- Handle debugging and troubleshooting to ensure the program functions correctly.
- Develop applications or systems to create software based on user requirements.
- Software Development.
- Create UI using Flutter.

Education

Bachelor of Computer: Sistem Informasi (2013 – 2018)

Universitas Raharja

Vocational High School: **Software Engineering (2010 – 2013)**

SMKN 5 Tangerang